WWW.MY-SUBS.CO
Last night, I wanted a drink
so fucking bad.
Uh-uh. You are five years sober.
What if I just can't
fucking do this anymore?
_
How are ya? Having fun?
You have the most
beautiful skin I've ever seen!
We gotta go.
Girls! You left your...
You guys made a mistake.
Just own up to your mistake.
It's all I'm asking.
I wrote a profile about you.
"Ten Power Women in the Tech World."
- That was a hatchet job.
- What?
Some lady found this on the beach
and gave it to me.
- What? No tag?
- No.
Have you ever thought
about starting like your own business?
Come on.
I would be down for funding
something like that.
Who's the guy you were with
by the lobby? I saw you.
He's just some random
who tried to pick me up.
Your dad didn't die from cancer.
He died from AIDS.
AIDS?
_
- Synced and corrected by Darrow -
- www.MY-SUBS.com -
Paula?
Hey.
Where were you?
I just walked around.
Couldn't sleep. Probably the K.
Fuck. Fuck! Fuck!
Fuck!
Shit!
Your father, Mark, he had sex with men.
He had two lives.
He had his family,
and then he had another life
with homosexuals.
Shit.
Oh, fuck!
That was amazing.
Love you, Rach.
Love you, too.
I can't wait to fuck in Tahiti.
Hey! I love it when you call me.
I was just thinking about you.
About to head off
to class here in a minute.
Yeah, I just got to work myself.
You're never not at work.
Oh, you think I'm working hard now,
wait till I start my own business.
What are you talking about?
I don't know.
I think I'm getting ahead of myself.
There is, um...
There's this woman, this... this guest,
this rich white lady.
She... she took me out to dinner,
and she said if I wanted to start
my own wellness center,
she'd fund the whole thing.
Mom, you have to do that.
That fucking place exploits you, Mom.
If that lady says jump,
you say, "How high?"
I'm serious. Work it.
Get your own thing going.
You deserve it.
All right. We'll see. We'll see.
Keep me posted.
I will. I will. I love you.
I'll talk to you later. Okay?
Okay.
All right. Bye.
Armond.
Armond!
Oh...
You know I thought you were dead, right?
No, just got here a little early.
Had a cat nap.
I'm fine.
- You're fine?
- I'm fine.
Mom, why are you setting up in here
and not your own room?
Because I have a Zoom with China,
and I don't like
the background in there.
When's the big Zoom?
One.
I don't like it in here either.
This lighting makes me look freakish.
You sure it's the lighting?
Quinn. Where have you been?
I slept on the beach.
Why?
Because of them! Because they made me!
And now all my shit is gone.
What shit?
My phone, my Nintendo!
They got washed away.
My iPad got soaked. It's fucking ruined.
And now what the fuck
am I supposed to do?
I didn't tell him to sleep on the beach.
It was his idea, Nicole.
They're lying!
Dad, what's wrong with you?
Your father got some very
upsetting news last night.
He does have cancer?
No. He doesn't have cancer.
He found out something about his father
that he never knew before.
I'm listening.
Your grandfather died of AIDS.
How did he get AIDS?
Apparently, Paula,
he was having sex with other men.
Who was?
Your dad's dad.
Why?
Because he liked it.
Why else? He was probably closeted.
Or bisexual.
Dad, why are you so upset, though?
You're like catatonic.
Well, it was a secret that was kept
from him his entire life, Liv.
So now, whatever image he had
of his father,
of his childhood, has been pulverized.
You know, he was probably a bottom.
That's how you mostly get it. Receiving.
Dad, do you feel like your father
was less of a man or something?
He might have not been gay.
A lot of straight guys like ass-play.
Yeah, maybe he was just too embarrassed
to ask Grandma to use a dildo on him.
Oh, Jesus!
Can we not, please? Uh...
Even if he wasn't a top,
it doesn't mean he was femme.
He could've still been butch, Dad.
Maybe he was a bossy bottom.
Yeah, maybe Grandpa was a power bottom.
Does that make you feel better?
No. That makes me wanna throw up.
Dad, you don't wanna say that.
Well, he can say whatever he wants.
You know, if he's having
a negative visceral reaction
to his father having gay sex,
it's valid.
It's fine.
Well, it comes off as homophobic.
Well, it's not.
Well, that's how it comes across.
Well, luckily, he's in a safe space
and he's here with our family
so he can come off however he wants.
Up to a point.
Or what? You'll cancel him?
Dox him? Sic the K-Pop fans on him?
See what I have to deal with?
Mom, I need a new phone, stat.
I'm gonna go completely insane.
You already are insane.
I'll order it for you right now.
So...
you were pretty horned up this morning.
Yeah.
Wake up next to you, what do you expect?
Is it a problem?
Aren't you horny for me?
- Yeah.
Yeah. Just not like every single minute.
Like you are.
Oh.
It's just not the most
important thing to me.
Well, what is?
Well, is it the most
important thing to you?
It's up there.
So the... this entire marriage
is just based on sex for you?
No. No.
Hey, all right.
Look, there's other stuff, too.
I love you.
And we're a team. We get along great.
- Uh...
- Yeah.
Oh my God.
You think that I'm like this... sex pig.
- Hey, look.
- No.
Me?
I can be romantic. I'm actually emo.
And don't put me in a box.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
Hey, buddy. Hold on a second.
Hey, if you see Armond,
could you tell him I'd like
to talk to him about something?
Of course.
It's not about the room.
Oh.
Hello.
How are you this morning?
I was hoping that you could help me.
I have something really important
that I need to do.
I brought my mother's ashes with me.
You know, so I could
spread them in the ocean.
And I just realized yesterday,
I'm gonna need a boat.
Oh, we have our resort boat
you can charter.
Is it free today?
'Cause I really need
to put this behind me.
Would you like to take it out at sunset?
Yeah, that would be nice.
Well, let's say, uh,
departure at 5:00 from the dock?
Can I get some alcohol on the boat?
I just... I think I might need a drink.
Of course. Some fruit and cheese, maybe?
Could you just tell the captain...
that I think I'm gonna be
a little emotional?
I just want him to be fully prepared.
Could be, like, a total basket case.
Well, see you at 5:00.
But let's definitely order the cheese.
- Mm-hmm.
- Thank you.
- Uh, Christie, could you cover the desk?
- Of course.
I just need to get
something from the office.
Sure. Not a problem.
- What?
- Uh, sorry.
I just wanted to tell you
that Mr. Patton
from the Palm Suite
wants to talk to you.
Are you fucking kidding me?
What?
He thinks we ruined his honeymoon?
Fuck him! I will ruin his honeymoon.
Well, he's eating by the pool, so...
I like your hair up like that.
Looks cute.
Um, thanks.
Can we have the phone sent here?
We're not here long enough.
It'll be there when we get home.
Then I'm gonna need
to use your computer, Mom.
Well, I do have work to do.
Like today,
I've got Zooms all afternoon.
What the fuck
am I supposed to do all day?
Enjoy Hawaii. Get in the ocean.
The o...
I did see a whale
last night on the beach.
That was pretty cool.
Well, you're not
sleeping out there again.
Mom, he likes it.
He's communing with nature.
It's funny how you're able
to have so much compassion
for all these groups
of oppressed peoples
you don't even know,
and yet not for your family.
Yep, okay.
Who actually know you and love you.
Your generation's only sacred value.
- Biting the hand that feeds you.
- Whatever.
- Hey, Dad.
- What?
You're not eating anything.
I'm not hungry.
That's your second Bloody Mary.
So?
We have scuba after this.
I'll be fine.
That's the guy.
Oh, man.
Excuse me, dude.
Aloha, ladies. How are you this morning?
Uh, yesterday I told you
about a bag. It's my friend's.
Yeah. I left it on the beach.
It's olive green.
I checked with, uh,
lost and found in the office,
and I'm so sorry to tell you,
it wasn't there.
But we'll keep an eye out.
And if it turns up,
I will call your room immediately.
I do hope we find it.
Aloha, Mr. Ross.
Uh, Lana will take you to table nine.
Thanks, Lana.
All right.
- I've been lookin' for ya.
- Mr. Patton.
- Hey.
- How are we this morning?
Yeah, no complaints.
Ah, love to hear that.
Um, listen, I wanna do
something special for my wife,
something kinda romantic.
It's our honeymoon.
I'm thinking a candlelit dinner
totally off on our own.
Somewhere cool that's like...
a beach or a cliff or just like...
like an Instagram spot, you know?
Yes. Yes. How wonderful.
- Yeah.
- Um...
And of course, we do private dinners
for couples all the time,
but since you're such valued guests,
and with the whole mix-up
regarding your room,
I would love to come up
with something really unique.
Okay, great. Yeah. That's...
that's what I'm thinking, too.
What about...
a candlelit dinner
on our charter boat at sunset?
That sounds perfect.
You can watch the sunset
from a private cove.
Oh!
Schools of dolphins leaping
and circling the boat
as you cruise the coastline,
- sipping piña coladas...
- Nice.
...debating the names
of your future offspring.
I... I don't know about that.
- Well, that sound like a plan?
- Yeah.
Well, see you down at the dock at 5:00.
Okay, great.
- Tonight then.
- Yeah. Thanks.
Oh, one little thing.
Uh, there will be
one other guest on the boat.
Really?
Yeah. Very lovely woman,
traveling alone,
and because she paid for the boat,
you'll only have to pay for the dinner.
- Oh, yeah?
- It's a sizable boat.
You won't even notice she's there.
She'll be quiet as a church mouse.
Yeah. All right. Yeah, that sounds fine.
I just...
I just want it to have a romantic vibe.
Absolutely. Oh, your wife is very lucky.
Thank you for all the help.
Of course.
Yes, we can do
the total relaxation package for you,
not a problem.
Actually, can I give you a call
right back?
- Hey!
- Hey.
Thank you again for dinner last night.
Really, I had a great time.
And it was cool, you know,
getting to know you more.
Yeah. You know, tonight's the night
I put my mother into the sea.
Oh, wow.
The boat leaves at 5:00.
I'd really appreciate
if you could be there.
I'm here until 7:00.
Oh, geez. Well, uh...
You know what? I'll take care of it.
I'm... I'm sure one of the girls
will be able to cover for me.
This is important.
I wanna be there for you.
Oh, thank you. Thank you.
Yeah.
And just so you know,
I'm probably gonna be a little drunk,
so don't judge me, all right?
- No.
- Okay.
No, I'd never.
Boat leaves at 5:00.
- Five o'clock.
- All right.
I'll see you.
All right.
Dad.
What?
If you don't feel
like doing this now, it's fine.
Nah.
It's just like...
What is real? Like, what...
You know? What's real?
Are you gay?
No.
Hey. 'Cause if you are, it's okay.
Just, like, be real.
I am being real.
What's real is...
like, gay, straight, whatever,
we're just monkeys,
we're just fucking monkeys.
Yeah?
Yeah. Yeah, we're just animals.
I mean, you know, we wanna be, like...
superheroes and respectable fathers
and pillars in our communities,
whatever, but... but in fact,
we're just monkeys...
living in our own little monkey pods,
driven by base instincts
to create these hierarchies
and hump each other.
I thought I knew my father, you know?
I only knew the part
that he wanted me to see.
He hid the monkey,
and that screwed me up, Quinn.
You think that's what did it?
Yeah, definitely.
Hey, I thought...
My whole life, I thought I was
the flawed child of an icon.
Like, I put him on this,
like, enormous pedestal.
Meanwhile, like,
he's off in some bathhouse on the DL,
getting manhandled by some...
like, random dudes.
Wow.
Oh, I wish I had known.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
But I get it. I mean, you know,
you don't want your kid thinking
you're some sex-crazed lunatic.
The room is... is beautiful,
and we have this ocean view,
and we face west,
so we get these incredible sunsets.
Yeah.
You'd love Hawaii. Everything's so lush.
Where we are, it isn't so overdeveloped.
And there's all of this
amazing food and pastries.
Hey.
So, yesterday you were reading
Freud and Nietzsche,
and today you're reading what?
Oh.
So you finished Freud and Nietzsche.
Are you actually reading
any of these books?
No, they're just props.
We have a stylist choose our outfits
and then we have a book stylist
pick out our books.
Yeah. That's what I figured.
Yeah, it's really relaxing.
I really wanna bring you and Dad here.
Are you gonna get in the water?
Ye... well... you... you do!
I mean, everyone takes vacations.
Okay, so sixty pages,
based on how fast you read,
that'll be like two minutes,
and then you can jump in.
Do you wanna know me?
May... maybe.
Do you?
I don't know.
Maybe it's better
if I'm just really real with you.
Maybe that's the healthier legacy.
I think it is. Yeah.
You guys ready to get your tanks on?
Yeah, let's do it!
Hey, if you won't come to the pool,
the pool is gonna come to you.
Get in.
Oh, my God!
Get in the water, come on!
Oh my God!
You got my book wet.
Oh my God.
Tastes a little like pee.
- I think it's your own.
- It's your own.
I think I forgot that I peed, yeah.
- Okay. Thank you.
- Sit wherever you like,
- I'll be right over.
- Thanks.
Yeah.
Get me the Kahuna with guac. All right?
I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
I'll be right back.
Enjoying your time?
Hi.
Oh, yeah. Hi. Uh, yes.
Yeah. Very much.
Honeymoon, yeah?
- Mm-hmm.
- Oh.
- And after this, we go to Tahiti.
- Thank you.
- Oh, that'll be nice.
- Yeah.
Where was your honeymoon?
Uh, believe it or not, we went to China.
Cool.
Nicole, my wife,
she took Mandarin in college,
so she wanted to show off.
It was... it was cool.
We went all around.
It was a lot different back then.
Yeah. China.
- Sure.
- Yeah.
How long ago was that?
Twenty-two years we've been married.
Twenty-two? That's impressive.
I guess.
I mean, I've got friends that, you know,
have been married, divorced,
married, divorced, so...
We're still going. So you never know.
So, what's your guys' secret?
How do you keep the spark alive?
Oh, the spark.
No, it's not alive. It died.
Yeah. I mean, love may be alive,
but spark...
Sure. That happens.
Yeah.
And his handstands.
He was totally trying to flash us.
Yeah, but with what?
Thumb dick.
What the fuck?
Oh, good. Hi, girls.
Can you just help me move this bed in?
I just... I just need
to do it real quick.
Mom, there's meds for this.
No, it's just for my Zoom.
I finally found a good background,
but I can see the bed.
So what?
Well, so I don't want
my entire organization
and my Chinese affiliates knowing
that I'm on fucking vacation!
Olivia, can you just help me
with the bed, please?
- I have five minutes.
- Okay, fine!
Thank you.
Okay. All right, girls, ready?
One, two, three.
Just lift it!
Push.
Oh, oh, yes, yes, yes, yes!
Are you okay, Paula?
No.
All right, I'm gonna start my Zoom.
And you guys,
if you're gonna stay in here,
you have to be totally silent.
Okay? And stay out of the frame.
Mom, you look deranged.
It's all right.
I have a filter for that.
Oh, fuck.
I chased Nicole for three years,
and she wouldn't let me touch her.
And then when I finally could,
I couldn't get enough, man. I was...
I had to have it all the time.
She thought I was nuts.
She thought that I should see a doctor.
She thought I had, uh...
priapism.
Which is like when... Hey, bud.
When you get this perpetual hard-on,
like an erection that you...
will not go down.
Yeah.
But after a few years,
it doesn't matter how much
role playing you do or, like,
toys you buy or porn
you watch together, whatever,
sex just turns into, like, a...
You know like when they do
one of those food challenges
on a reality show,
you know, where they gotta, like,
eat like a bowl of live worms,
and you just got...
you gotta psych yourself up for it.
You're like, "I can do this.
Just hold my nose and, like,
suck it down as fast as I can
so I don't gag."
Yeah.
But it's natural.
I mean, it'd be weird
if it didn't fade, you know.
Look, I'm just being real
with you, you know.
Oh, this is my son, Quinn. And I'm Mark.
Right. Hi.
What are you talking about?
Nothing. Sex with your mom.
You know, I actually...
I think I'm gonna order
from the room just 'cause it's...
It's so hot here.
I'm feeling hot.
Well, it was nice to talk with you.
And I hope that you have
a great honeymoon.
Thank you.
And you guys have a great trip.
Okay? Bye. Thanks.
Was it something I said?
Shit!
Olivia, get down!
Ow.
Hey, everybody.
Nicole Mossbacher. Good to see you all.
Hey!
You left me.
I'm surprised that you noticed.
What? Oh, shut up!
You were so busy
flirting with those girls.
I was not flirting with those girls.
I was giving them shit.
Well, it certainly seemed
like you were having a good time.
Aw. Is my baby jealous?
No.
Whatever.
Yeah.
Well, I came to find you to tell you
to wear something extra cute tonight.
What do you mean? Why?
I got a little something planned.
Tell me.
- No.
- Tell me.
It's a surprise.
Tell me.
But I will tell you, it is very,
very, very romantic.
It's natural to want something new.
I mean, when you're jerking to porn,
do you watch the same clip every time?
No. Never.
I think I'm gonna go.
Yeah? Okay.
Um, can I borrow your phone?
Mine's gone, and I need to get online.
Uh... all right.
See you back in the room.
Who are these people?
They're joining for dinner.
I hope that's okay.
Oh, all right.
Watch your step!
- Aloha!
- Hi. Aloha.
- Thank you.
- Oh! Wow!
Is this all for us?
- Uh, yeah. Yeah. Pretty much.
- Yeah?
I'll hold that for you.
Oh, thank you so much. I love this.
Hey, everybody.
- Hey!
- Hey.
Thank you for coming.
I know I don't know you,
but I'm glad you're here.
Well, these are my mother's ashes.
And I just wanna say that, you know,
I don't want tonight to be a downer.
You know, my mother would've wanted us
to have a good time.
So let's have fun, okay?
I think I need to set this down.
- This is nice.
- Yeah.
- Get a little tan.
- It's getting warmer.
- Hi.
Quick question. Uh, what's...
what's going on here?
Just, uh, just refilled your drink.
Right. No, I know what this is.
Um, what's going on with this lady?
- What's...
- Oh, um...
She's planning on scattering
her mother's ashes off the boat.
Okay. Does she think
we're here for that?
'Cause we're not.
Shane...
Do you want me to speak to her?
- Oh, no, no, no.
- Well...
It's fine. No. It's... it's fine.
Everything's okay. Thank you so much.
Of course. Mahalo.
- Mahalo.
We can't... we can't tell her
not to bother us.
Like, well, I'm trying to have
a romantic time with my wife.
Hey!
- Hi.
You guys wanna sit up here?
Yeah. No, that's okay. Thank you.
It might be more convivial.
We're on our honeymoon.
- Hmm.
- Thank you, though.
Oh my gosh.
How nice to be in love.
Mm. Mm. Yeah.
I wish I had a man here.
I mean, you know, I...
I'm really happy you're here.
You know what I mean.
I totally get it.
Woo-hoo!
All right.
You're a beautiful couple.
- Leprosy is no joke.
- It's not.
You know about leprosy, right?
- Right, totally.
- Yeah?
That's a weird nerve disease
where they have...
they, like, they can't even feel like...
You could get hit by a bus...
- Hey! What're you doing?
- Hey, baby, where've you been?
...and not even know it.
- Yeah.
- Let's go.
- You wanna get out of here?
- Yeah. Totally.
See ya.
Bye.
Whiskey, neat.
Yeah, you got it, boss.
Drinking on the job?
Done for the day.
Oh.
Where's your family?
Oh, shit. I should get back to them.
Um...
No, they've seen enough of me.
Thirsty?
Long day.
Yeah. Me, too.
I can be romantic. See, right?
- Yeah.
- I mean...
Totally. Thank you.
You didn't have to do this, though.
I wanted to.
But is it because
of our conversation this morning?
I guess I just get insecure, like...
if our whole thing is based
on your sexual attraction to me,
then what happens
when that attraction fades?
Baba.
it is not going to fade.
- No?
- No.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
Hi. I think it's time.
So you guys are gonna have
to get up, okay?
- Oh.
- Yes.
Will you mo... move their table?
Of course, Ms. MacQuoid.
Oh, ow! Hold on! Can I just...
We can just...
That's fine, move it this way.
- Watch where you're going.
- Sorry, Ms. MacQuoid.
- Yeah. I just...
- Got it?
Yeah, I got it. All right. There we go.
- Okay, thank you.
- Yeah.
All right.
My poor mother...
she died in June.
And she loved the ocean. Just loved it.
My poor mother,
she had a beautiful house in Carmel.
And she tried very, very hard
to be a really good mother,
even though she didn't have
any maternal instincts or skills.
She, uh, she was always
in search of male affection.
And, uh, she was...
a nymphomaniac.
I'd walk in her room and I'd find
all sorts of strange men in her bed.
She had borderline personality disorder.
She took her money
and she manipulated people with it.
And she was cruel.
And she was very, very cruel.
She was so, so cruel and...
I... I just... oh, mother,
mother, mother, mother.
My mother...
told me I would never be a ballerina,
and that was when I was skinny.
My poor mother, she...
She just couldn't handle her jealousy.
She had to take me down.
And what's weird is I miss my mother
even though she was a big jerk!
I just... I need your help, everybody.
I... I've been trying for many days now
to open this box.
My poor mother's in here.
I need someone to help me.
Do you want me to open the box?
Yeah, I would love that.
I'll get it.
Um...
Yeah. Just...
Oh my God, thank you.
Yeah, no big deal. Yeah.
Mother.
Goodbye, Mother.
Goodbye, Mother!
I can't... I can't do this.
You know, this is...
I just realized it's too early for me.
It's okay.
All right.
Oh, I want my mother, mother, mother.
- Oh, I can't.
- Hey let's, uh, yeah... maybe...
- Why don't we... yeah, back in the box.
- I wanted my...
- Oh, my God.
- It's okay.
- It's totally okay.
- Oh my God.
No, it's not okay!
I don't understand
what happened to your father.
I mean, I've been texting him all day.
I have his phone.
Well, you could've
told me that earlier, Quinn.
You know, this is all because of you,
because you won't share
a giant room with your brother.
Mom, it works out perfect.
He can have the entire beach
to himself to jerk off.
I don't jerk...
Finish your sentence.
Whatever.
You're addicted to porn.
- No, I'm not.
- Yes, you are.
Don't sex shame him.
Boys are sex shamed all the time now.
I mean, I know it's very in,
but it's not okay.
What?
You sex shame Dad.
I do not.
Okay. Whatever gets you
through the night.
You... you're gay, right?
Yes, I'm gay.
No, my father was gay.
I think. He, uh, he had sex with men.
That's a telltale sign.
- Hey, can I ask you a question?
- Hmm.
What's it like, like, you know,
being fucked up the ass?
Like, is that...
I mean, it must feel kinda good,
otherwise you wouldn't
keep doing it, right?
Does... does it feel good?
Do you wanna find out?
Uh, no, I'll take a rain check.
Hutch.
When you're young,
sex is powerful and intoxicating.
And as we mature, it gets demystified.
You realize there are
more important things to focus on.
Like what? Zooming with China?
Like holding onto whatever
shreds of dignity you still have.
That's so perverted.
Can I take these?
Yes, thank you.
If you had the phone,
did you see me texting all day?
And you didn't respond, Quinn?
He did not tell us
that she chartered that boat
for a goddamn funeral!
- It's okay.
- No, it's not okay!
He did it on purpose.
He's fucking gaslighting me.
- You have to let it go.
- I'm not gonna let it go.
What I wanna do is go find that fucker.
Shane.
Okay, one second, let me just...
- What?
- There you go.
- On the count of three.
- Okay.
One, two, three. There you go. Good.
You're a beautiful woman.
Oh, thank you, Tanya.
Is it... Okay! You got it.
Let's just get the bottom half
to join you.
There you go. Okay. All right.
- My head.
- Oh.
- Let's...
Oh yeah.
- That's...
- Oh... oh, oh!
There you go.
- All right.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Good night to her,
and good night to you.
Everything's gonna be okay.
- Mm-hmm?
- Mm-hmm!
You got it.
Yes?
Hi.
How was the cruise?
Not good.
Great.
Actually, it was a shit show.
They're fucking pissed.
Perfect.
Oh, do you want a drink?
I, uh, I have tequila.
I have, uh... other things.
Uh, no, no, I'm good.
I like this new hair look.
Yeah. Yeah. You said that already.
Turns out you're my type.
Blonde surfer with a man bun.
Okay.
You're a great worker, Dillon.
Oh, um, well, thank you.
I have my eyes on you.
Okay. Well, I will talk to you later.
All right. I'll see you...
I was texting you all day,
and then Quinn told me
he had your phone.
Hmm, mm-hmm.
You're taking this really hard.
Why would he be gaslighting you?
This has happened before.
Like, people have been coming for me
my whole life.
I'm just playing the hand I was dealt.
Like, yeah. It's a great hand.
And that's not my fault.
Shane. Don't worry about it.
I loved our dinner.
I thought it was really romantic...
until it wasn't.
Yeah.
Don't. I'm not in the mood.
I'm just kidding.
I'm always in the mood.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Come on.
Okay.
Get off me, monkey.
Get off me. I mean it.
Yeah. Mm, yeah.
- Synced and corrected by Darrow -
- www.MY-SUBS.com -
Ooh.
Surprise!
Mom!
Am I interrupting?
It's only your honeymoon!
What are you doing here?!
_
It's like we're the underdogs now.
He's a white man,
and nobody has any sympathy for them.
- I think he's gonna be okay, Nicole.
- Thank you, Paula.
- This is the spa.
- I got asked out.
He's a deep-sea fisherman
from Black Lives Matter.
Here's another treat. Enjoy.
Dad, I think that guy
was hitting on you.
He was just, you know, being friendly.
Baba, tell my mom
what you were thinking about.
I really want to get a job.
No, why would you do that?
_
When we meet Tanya,
she has this big box of ashes.
I brought my mother's ashes with me,
so I could spread them in the ocean.
I'm gonna need a boat.
We have our resort boat you can charter.
I think I'm gonna be a little emotional.
You can sense there's just a lot
of internal drama about it,
and it's like she's desperate
to get rid of them
and she's also attached.
You know, tonight's the night
I put my mother into the sea.
Oh, wow.
I'd really appreciate it
if you'd be there.
I'll take care of it.
I'm sure one of the girls
would be able to cover for me.
This is important.
I want to be there for you.
Tanya sort of represents how we can all
be kind of a mess sometimes,
and I think it provokes empathy
from Belinda
and causes Belinda
to let down her boundaries.
You were pretty horned up this morning.
Weren't you horny for me?
It's just not the most
important thing to me.
Well, what is?
Well, is it the most
important thing to you?
It's up there.
There's humor
to what they're going through
just because it's such
an obvious problem.
He's not hearing her at all.
All she wants is to be heard,
but she doesn't know
how to get him to understand.
I think Shane really loves Rachel,
but I don't think he digs that deep.
When he's happy, the world is good,
so some of the identity crisis
that she's experiencing
and some of the anxious elements to her,
he doesn't get it.
I wanna do something special,
something kinda romantic.
What about a candlelit dinner
on our charter boat?
- Thank you.
- Oh, wow.
There will be
one other guest on the boat.
You won't even notice she's there.
She'll be quiet as a church mouse.
Armond sending Shane out on this
boat ride is definitely calculated.
He thinks we've ruined his honeymoon?
I will ruin his honeymoon!
But I'm not sure
that he would've done it
if he wasn't now high.
It unlocks in the character
this ability to really, like,
act on what he actually wants to do.
Turns out you're my type.
I have my eyes on you.
Later, Shane says to Rachel...
He did it on purpose.
People have been coming for me
my whole life.
He is aggressive and entitled,
but realizing someone has been
intentionally ruining my time here.
He's validated in his exasperation.
I thought I knew my father, meanwhile,
he's getting manhandled
by some random dudes.
Mark is definitely
on a roller coaster ride
with who his father was
and what that means.
Gay, straight, whatever,
we're just monkeys.
Yeah.
We're just animals
driven by base instincts to...
create these hierarchies
and hump each other.
To Quinn, some of his struggles
seem ridiculous and unpleasant.
Oh, I wish I'd known.
But some of it really is
interesting and moving.
I'm sorry.
In episode three,
he's really spiraling out.
He's day drinking
and starting to chat up
girls that are half his age.
- Leprosy is no joke.
- It's not.
He goes on kind
of a dark day of the soul.
You're taking this really hard.
In the end, you realize
what he's really looking for
is some kind of masculine validation.
Get off me.
Can I take these?
Yes, thank you.
Kai is
a young gentleman from Hawaii
who works at the White Lotus.
Paula, as soon as she sees him,
is instantly drawn to him
and attracted to him
and does not really
disclose that to Olivia.
Where were you?
I just walked around.
They're sort of twinning
at the beginning,
but then you realize,
over the course of the show,
that there's actually
a big gap between them that grows
as the mysteries
of their relationship unfold.
You can see how everyone's behavior
affects each other
and how these relationships
have slowly evolved
because of who each of these people are
and how they treat one another.
_